Guide to the Student Association records, 1935-2005 RG0023
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Student Association records
1935-2005
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
George Washington University. Student Association
RG0023
25 Linear Feet
Collection includes legislative records, governing documents, by-laws, student court cases, Greek policy, minutes and memos, records, and correspondence. freshmen register, homecoming and campaign posters, and constitutional convention records.
Restrictions on Access
Collection is open for use.
Acquisition Information
Materials acquired through transfers from the Student Association and from donations by individual alumni, as noted at the series level.
Historical or Biographical Note
Prior to the Student Association, the student governing body was the student council. The Student Association was established in April 1976. Membership included all full-time, part-time, graduate, professional and undergraduate students who were registered for academic credit. Today, the Student Association is made up of the executive, senate and judicial branches.
This was written in 2005.
Collection Scope and Content
Materials in this collection include legislative records, governing documents, by-laws, student court cases, Greek policy, Marvin Center, athletics, budget, Senate minutes and memos. The collection also includes senate finance, reports to the Board of Trustees, Senate-elect meetings, senate meetings, roll call votes, senate administrative records, Tony Sayegh's records, Eric Daleo's records, correspondence, minutes, Mortar board, constitution membership logs, scrapbook, brochures, freshmen register, homecoming and campaign posters, and alumnus Barry Epstein's Constitutional Convention papers. The collection covers the years 1935-2005. Note: Not all series are processed. Ask staff for assistance.
Collection Organization
Organized into 11 series: Mortar Board society, Freshmen register, Posters, Photo directory, Student Association files, Meeting minutes, Student Association files, Student government records, Barry Epstein Constitutional Convention and Student Association papers, Joint Committee election records, and Kuyomars "Q" Golparvar collection of student association records.
Finance; Scrapbooks; Greek letter societies; Elections; By-laws; Legislation; Sports; Washington (D.C.); Student government; George Washington University
- Mortar Board society, 1941-1976; RG0023 Series 1; 2 Linear feet (Box 1, Flat box 3, Box 2)
  Scope and Contents note
  This series consists of Mortar Board (Hour Glass society) constitution, by-laws, oath, membership log, meeting minutes, scrapbook, banner, and brochures. The materials range in date from 1941-76.
  Formerly ACC#310.
- Freshmen register, 1970-1988; RG0023 Series 2; 1 Linear foot (Box 1, Box 2)
  This series consists of the freshmen register, which listed incoming freshman and photos of them. The materials range in date from 1970-98.
- Posters, 1994-1995; RG0023 Series 3; 0.25 Linear feet (Map-folder 1)
  This series consists of a Student Association homecoming poster and campaign posters. The materials range in date from 1994-95.
- Photo directory, 1966-1967; RG0023 Series 4; 0.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series consists of a photo directory of new students, including transfers. The materials range in date from1966-67. This was the predecessor of the freshmen register.
- Student Association files, 1991-2000; RG0023 Series 5; 6 Linear feet (Box 4, Box 3, Box 2, Box 1)
  This series consists of legislative records, governing documents, by-laws, student court cases, greek policy, Marvin Center, budget records, senate minutes, memos, audio tapes. The materials range in date from 1991-2000.
  - Legislative Binder - EVP Dave Parker, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Legislative Binder - EVPs Jonathon Tarnow & James Aresnault #1, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Legislative Binder - EVPs Jonathon Tarnow & James Aresnault #2, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Legislative Binder - EVP Paul Hamilton, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Legislative Binder - EVP Scott Slifka, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Governing Documents, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Legislative Binder - EVP Jonathon Koa, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Legislative Binder - EVP Dianne Guyoski, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Attendance Record - EVP Paul Hamilton, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Student Association Annual Report, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Senate Leadership, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Misc. Senate Folder - Campus Plan, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Misc. Senate Folder - Gargano Folder, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Misc. Senate Folder - Bylaws, 02/1999 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Misc. Senate Folder - Joint Committee of Faculty and Students, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Misc. Senate Folder - Forms, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Misc. Senate Folder - Parliamentary Procedure Info, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Student Court Cases - S 99 - 001, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Student Court Cases - S 99 - 002, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Student Court Cases - S 99 - 004, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Student Life Committee - Agendas, Minutes, Misc., 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Senate Misc. Folder, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Students First Report - Student First, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Students First Report - GAPSA, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Full Senate - Misc., 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Student Life Committee Agenda, Minutes, etc., 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Student Court Cases S 98 - 001, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Issue Awareness Nights II, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Greek Policy, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Marvin Center Governing Board, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Executive Branch, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Athletics & Recreation - Reports, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Athletics & Recreation - Health and Wellness Center, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Government Documents, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - SASS - Mike Gargano, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - SASS - SAC, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Community Affairs, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Budget, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Budget Cont'd - Tuition Commission, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Budget Cont'd - Petitions, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Budget Cont'd - Student Fee, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Budget Cont'd - Budget Info, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Programming, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Misc. Folder - Tuition Media, undated (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Misc. Folder - SBPP Tabulation, undated (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Misc. Folder - SBPP Surveys, undated (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Misc. Folder - TAC Bill, undated (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Budget, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Senates Minutes, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Security Affairs, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Community Service Report, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Student Life Legislation, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Academic Advising, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Parking & Recycling, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Student Life Committee - Minutes, Agendas, etc., undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Student Court Cases - S 97 001-007, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Student Court Cases Random, undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Academic Affairs Fair, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Misc. Folder, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Other Senate Legislation, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Student Life Committee Final Report, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Thurston ATM Project, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Issue Awareness Night, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Meisner Impeachment Proceedings, 11/1999 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Finance Committee, 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Academic Affairs Committee, 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Rules Committee, 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - General Surveys, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Budgetary Priority Survey, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Student Group Funding, 1995-1997 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Election Reform Committee, 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Memos, 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Senate Guide, 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Senate Resolutions, 1995-1996 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Senate Bills, 1995-1996 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Initial Allocations, undated (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Finance Committee, 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Senate Bills, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Senate Legislation, 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Revised Bylaws of the Student Association, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Report from the Association Counsel: University Student Financial Assistance Policy Study Group, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - President Musante's Response to GW Community Regarding his Racial Slur, undated (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Senate Minutes, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - "Proportional Representation Now": Petition (signed by 10% of student population) for referendum with accompanying letter by EVP Singer and Senators Daleo (CCAS-U) and Moss (SBPM-U), undated (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - 3 Audio Tapes: Senate Meetings (2/11/97, 2/25/97, and 3/11/97), 02/11/1997 -03/11/1997 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Meeting minutes, 1953-1969; RG0023 Series 6; 1 Linear foot (Box 1, Box 2)
  This series consists of meeting minutes from the student council. The materials range in date from 1953-69.
  - Student Council Minutes, 06/1953 -08/1953 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Student Council Minutes, 06/1957 -12/1957 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Student Council Minutes, 01/1958 -04/1958 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Student Council Minutes, 05/1958 -12/1958 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Student Council Minutes, 01/1959 -10/1959 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    General note
    Dates range from January-May 1959, September-October 1959.
  - Student Council Minutes, 01/1960 -03/1960 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Student Council Minutes, 06/1961 -12/1961 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Missing September
  - Student Council Minutes, 02/1962 -12/1962 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Missing May, June, September, and October
  - Student Council Minutes, 02/1963 -07/1963 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Student Council Minutes, 10/1963 -12/1963 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Student Council Minutes, 01/1964 -04/1964 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Student Council Minutes, 06/1964 -11/1964 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Missing July and August
  - Student Council Minutes, 02/1965 -04/1965 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Student Council Minutes, 09/1965 -10/1965 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Student Council Minutes, 02/1966 -11/1966 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Missing April, June, and August
  - Student Council Minutes, 02/1967 -05/1967 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Student Council Minutes, 09/1967 -12/1967 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Student Council Minutes, 01/1968 -09/1968 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Student Council Minutes, 02/1969 -03/1969 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Student Council Minutes, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Student Association files, 1992-2016; RG0023 Series 7; 7.5 Linear feet (Box 3, Box 2, Box 1, Box 5, Box 4)
  This series consists of senate finance files, report to the Board of Trustees, Senate meetings, roll call votes, senate administrative records, Tony Sayegh's records, Eric Daleo's records, correspondence, minutes, memos. The materials range in date from 1992-2004.
  - Senate Finance Binder, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Legislative Budget, Detailed Spending, and Expenditures
  - Senate Finance Binder, 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Change-in-Status Reports, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Committee Chair Reports Releasing SA Legislation
  - Change-in-Status Reports, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Student Association Report to the Board of Trustees, 02/06/2004 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - DC Metropolitan-University Student Alliance, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Binder on consortium of student govt's
  - Senate Voting and Attendance Tallies, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Senate-Elect Meeting Binder #2, 04/29/2003 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes, Reports, Correspondence, Special Announcements, Roll Call Vote Logs, Initial Public Comment Records
  - Senate Meeting Binder #1, 09/23/2003 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Senate Meeting Binder #2, 10/07/2003 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Senate Meeting Binder #3, 10/14/2003 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Senate Meeting Binder #4, 10/28/2003 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Senate Meeting Binder #5, 11/18/2003 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Senate Meeting Binder #6, 12/02/2003 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Senate Meeting Binder #7, 12/20/2003 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Senate Meeting Binder #1, 01/14/2004 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Senate Meeting Binder #2, 01/20/2004 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Senate Meeting Binder #3, 02/03/2004 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Senate Meeting Binder #4, 02/17/2004 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Senate Meeting Binder #5, 03/09/2004 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Senate Meeting Binder #6, 03/30/2004 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Senate Meeting Binder #7, 04/13/2004 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Senate Meeting Binder #7, 01/20/2003 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Senate Meeting Binder #8, 01/21/2003 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Senate Meeting Binder #9, 02/04/2003 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Senate Meeting Binder #10, 02/18/2003 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Senate Meeting Binder #11, 04/08/2003 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Senate Meeting Binder #12, 04/22/2003 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Meeting Packets, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Agendas, Minutes, Legislation, Committee Reports
  - Meeting Packets, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence File, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Outgoing and Incoming
  - Senate Administrative Binder, 2002-2003 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Publicity, Miscellaneous EVP Official, Resignation Letters, Outreach and Recruitment, Student Court & Executive Branch Documents
  - Senate Administrative Binder, 2003-2004 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence File, 2002-2003 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Tony E. Sayegh, Jr.'s Legislative Binder, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Agendas, Minutes, Resolutions, Bills, Roll Call Votes, Correspondence, Attendance Records
  - Tony E. Savegh Jr.'s Senate-Elect Meeting Binder, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Agendas, Minutes, Bills, Attendance Records, Proxies, Roll Call Votes, Resolutions
  - Assorted Folders and Documents, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Binder of Eric R. Daleo, CCAS-U Senator, 2001-2002 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Election campaigning material, 2016 (Flat box BOX 6)
  - Undergraduate Research Front Matter, 1987-2014; Series 7 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Undergraduate Research [1/2], 1987-2014; Series 7 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Undergraduate Research [2/2], 1987-2014; Series 7 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Publications Committee [1/2], 1987-2014; Series 7 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Publications Committee [2/2], 1987-2014; Series 7 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Front Pocket Matter: Unmarked-Marvin Center Governing Board, 1987-2014; Series 7 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Organization: Unmarked-Marvin Center Governing Board, 1987-2014; Series 7 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Unmarked Section: Unmarked-Marvin Center Governing Board, 1987-2014; Series 7 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Back Pocket Matter: Unmarked-Marvin Center Governing Board, 1987-2014; Series 7 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Front Pocket Matter: Incomplete EAFS 2011-2012, SA Finance.com 2013-2014 [1/2], 2011-2014; Series 7 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Front Matter: Incomplete EAFS 2011-2012, SA Finance.com 2013-2014 [2/2], 2011-2014; Series 7 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Manuals, Bylaws, etc.: Incomplete EAFS 2011-2012, SA Finance.com 2013-2014, 2011-2014; Series 7 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Meeting Agendas: Incomplete EAFS 2011-2012, SA Finance.com 2013-2014, 2011-2014; Series 7 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Meeting Minutes: Incomplete EAFS 2011-2012, SA Finance.com 2013-2014, 2011-2014; Series 7 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Unmarked Section: Incomplete EAFS 2011-2012, SA Finance.com 2013-2014 [1/2], 2011-2014; Series 7 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Unmarked Sections: Incomplete EAFS 2011-2012, SA Finance.com 2013-2014 [2/2], 2011-2014; Series 7 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Agendas: Senate-Elect 1998-1999 [1/7], Series 7 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Minutes: Senate-Elect 1998-1999 [2/7], Series 7 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Attendance: Senate Elect 1998-1999 [3/7], Series 7 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Memos: Senate Elect 1998-1999 [4/7], Series 7 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Handouts: Senate Elect 1998-1999 [5/7], Series 7 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Senate Elect Bill: Senate Elect 1998-1999 [6/7], 1987-2014; Series 7 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Miscellaneous Unmarked Section: Senate Elect 1998-1999 [7/7], Series 7 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Schedules: Senate Records 1998-1999 [1/8], Series 7 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Agendas: Senate records 1998-1999 [2/8], Series 7 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Minutes: Senate Records 1998-1999 [3/8], Series 7 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Legislation: Senate Records 1998-1999 [4/8], Series 7 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Attendance: Senate Records 1998-1999 [5/8], Series 7 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Handouts: Senate Records 1998-1999 [6/8], Series 7 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Resignations: Senate Records 1998-1999 [7/8], Series 7 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Miscellaneous: Senate Records 1998-1999 [8/8], Series 7 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Senate Bills and Resolution [1/2], 2008-2011; Series 7 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Senate Bills and Resolution [2/2], 2008-2011; Series 7 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Senate Documents, 2008-2011; Series 7 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Student Affairs Committee [1/2], 1997-1998; Series 7 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Students Affairs Committee [2/2], 1997-1998; Series 7 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Faculty Senate 2004-2005, 2003-2004; Series 7 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Senate Meetings #5 through #7 and Committee Documents [1/4], 2005-2006; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Senate Meetings #5 through #7 and Committee Documents [2/4], 2005-2006; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Senate Meetings #5 through #7 and Committee Documents [3/4], 2005-2006; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Senate Meetings #5 through #7 and Committee Documents [4/4], 2005-2006; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Athletics, 17 May 2007; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: SA Board of Trustees, 17 May 2007; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Dean of Freshmen, 17 May 2007; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Marvin Center, 17 May 2007; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Housing, 17 May 2007; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: SASS Financial Report, 17 May 2007; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Student and Academic Support Services, 17 May 2007; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: GW Police Department, 17 May 2007; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Report to the Board of Trustees, 17 May 2007; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Office of Admissions, 17 May 2007; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Meeting Agenda, 17 May 2007; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Minutes-Thursday, February 8, 2007, 17 May 2007; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Back Pocket Matter, 20 October 2005; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Communications and Creative Services/University Police Department, 20 October 2005; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Dean of Freshmen Portfolio, 20 October 2005; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Assistant VP Portfolio, 20 October 2005; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Admission/Financial Aid, 20 October 2005; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Committee Mission Statement, 20 October 2005; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Student Association, 20 October 2005; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Athletics, 20 October 2005; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Dean of Students Portfolio, 20 October 2005; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: University Strategic Plan, 20 October 2005; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Minutes-May 19, 2005, 20 October 2005; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Front Pocket Matter, 20 October 2005; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Back Pocket Matter, 13 May 2004; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: SASS Research, 13 May 2004; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: SASS communication Technology, 13 May 2004; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Associate VP and Dean of Freshmen, 13 May 2004; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Student Association, 13 May 2004; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Athletics, 13 May 2004; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Dean of Student Portfolio, 13 May 2004; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Student Activities Center, 13 May 2004; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Financial Assistance, 13 May 2004; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Undergraduate Admissions, 13 May 2004; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Minutes-February 5, 2004, 13 May 2004; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Front Pocket Matter, 13 May 2004; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: SASS Communication and Technology, 16 October 2003; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Extra! Extra!-Dean of Students, Student Activities Center, and Parent Services, 16 October 2003; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Student Association: It's all about the students, 16 October 2003; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Athletics-Breaking News in A-10 (or not!), 16 October 2003; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Transportation-A Voyage on the Colonial Express and GW Shuttle, 16 October 2003; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Freshmen and International Student Service at Foggy Bottom and Foxhall Road, 16 October 2003; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Housing-Looking from the ivory Tower with the BZA in mind, 16 October 2003; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Student Financial Assistance-The context and challenges of financing a GW education, 16 October 2003; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Admissions-Trends and Challenges in the New Frontier, 16 October 2003; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Minutes-May 15, 2003, 16 October 2003; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Back Pocket Matter, 15 May 2003; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Student Financial Assistance, 15 May 2003; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: SASS Communication and Technology, 15 May 2003; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Marvin Center and Student Activities Center, 15 May 2003; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Dean of Student Portfolio, 15 May 2003; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Student Affairs Committee 2000-2007: Title Nine Update, Athletics and Recreation, 15 May 2003; Series 7 (Box 8, Folder 56)